PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Innovating, creating, engaging, and advocating. I believe in always building, maintaining, and representing the user experience. You want me on your team because I balance independence with collaboration. I am driven and passionate about what I do, taking initiative to be the subject matter expert and connect teams together. I work well under pressure and prove that ownership creates outcomes. You need my passion, attention to detail, and ability to transform complexity into simplicity.

I am here to disrupt.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

NLP INTERACTION DESIGNER - FIDELITY INVESTMENTS: 2018-PRESENT

Application designer, content strategist, UX analyst, and front-end developer for agentBOT:

- Leading the strategy and execution of an eight-person content team
- Connecting the team/business partners to our users, and designing the product's interaction
- Developing HTML and JavaScript enhancements and fixes within the agentBOT Angular application
- Leading the effort to define the Branding and Experience of the agent**BOT** application: interface, logo, and communications
- Analyzing user trends and conducting primary user research to understand behaviors
- Owning Squad KPIs as defined through content coverage and content positioning

DESIGN LEAD - FIDELITY DIGITAL ASSETS, TADPOLE: 2017-2018

Customer experience, product, and design analyst for Project Tadpole:

- Leading user research, branding, and competitive landscape projects
- Designing and testing UI changes with users
- Connecting and working across multiple business units throughout the firm

CREATIVE DESIGN ASSOCIATE - FIDELITY INVESTMENTS: 2016-2017

Design lead, project lead, and key contributor. Enhancing the customer experience through voice design development:

- Managing and leading team contributions on various NLP (Natural Language Processing) application initiatives including MyVoice, Service-to-Sales, HAVA, and Self-Service Transformation
- Creating and facilitating design trainings
- Conducting Primary User Research

FINANCIAL TRADER - FIDELITY INVESTMENTS: 2014-2017

Licensed financial professional in High Net Worth and Electronic Response:

- Providing exceptional customer service on both a financial and personal level
- Consistently a top performer and CEI ambassador

PROJECT MANAGER, DESIGN ANALYST - RSI INC: 2012-2014

Project manager, user analyst, and media/communications director for CEO Dick Simon:

- Writing a TEDxBeaconStreet Talk
- Creating the kNOwTHEM Initiative
 - Responsible for article writing, community outreach, and social media
- Writing and editing the kNOwTHEM Initiative's Parallel Narratives Series
 - Collection of educational essays comparing nations' varying histories
- Head of curriculum creation and media production for YPO Art of Peace Conflict Resolution

SYSTEMS & TOOLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Angular
- VSCode
- Sketch
- Premiere Pro/Adobe Suite

AFFILIATIONS

- Transgender Advocacy Group Global Co-Lead: 2018-Current
- Pride Utah Regional Co-Lead: 2017-Current

SCRUM WORK

User Designer, Associate Mobile Application – 2017:

- Developing the new associate mobile application, focusing on design, development, and testing

User Researcher, Consultant, Efficient Solutions Team – 2017:

- Leading associate design sessions and research efforts to reduce call volumes by 20%

Field SME, FocusPoint Training – 2017:

- SME for L&D and technology partnership working within FocusPoint and associate tools

Field SME, Sally Experience – 2017:

- SME to Sally Experience Team, developing customer profile capabilities

EDUCATION

University of Utah – 2019:

- Full Stack Development Certificate

Brigham Young University, BA – 2013:

- Major: Middle Eastern Studies/Arabic
- Minor: Women's Studies
- Honors: Women's Studies Honor Society Board

NOTABLE PROJECTS

Abby Johnson and Senior Executive Team Presentations – 2017, 2018, 2019:

- Al Powered-Solutions
- agentBOT
- Fidelity Digital Assets
- The Power of the Associate and Customer Advocacy

Know Your Customer – Profile Personalization – 2016-2019:

- Creating the initiative for customer profile personalization
- Re-designing the Fid.com Customer Profile page and associate tools

Jordan Study Abroad - 2011:

- Intensive Arabic language program
- Studying Jordanian and Palestinian women's issues in-country